hey guys welcome to this video we're
going to solve and graph these the way
you handle this type of problem is
solved for x for each of these three add
5 for X is less than 40 and divided by
4x is less than 10 we'll do the same
thing here minus 4 negative X is less
than or equal to negative 14 divided by
negative 1 and we get x + 14 and anytime
you multiply it or divide by a negative
number you switch the sign so you can't
forget to switch the sign and then we
saw the word and here so and means we
want to know when they are both true so
let's graph this tried to show zero to
10 and the 14 not to scale and I'm sure
many other numbers this pretty much
tells the story 10 is an open circle
because it does not include it and it
says X is less than 10 so I'm going to
go this way and then X greater than or
equal to 14 I'm going to shade the
circle in because it's greater than or
equal to so the equal to means is shaded
in and I'm going to go this way because
X is greater than it so the word and
means we want both of them to be true in
this case both are never true so the
answer is no solution or it could also
be empty set depending on your teacher
so let's answer the question hope that
makes sense please like and subscribe
check out aunty Matt Kong for more
videos and notes and I'll talk to you
guys soon bye
you